hash-master.com 2015-04-29

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our website, we value and appreciate your interest. Our Privacy Policy is intended to protect your privacy and provide you with a safe and secure experience using our website. Below, please find our Privacy Policy.

USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you opt into our email list, register your appliance for warranty coverage or make a purchase through [www.hash-master.com](http://www.hash-master.com/), the information you provide (for example, name, address, and email address) will be added to a database. HASH MASTER, Inc. may use that information for our own internal marketing purposes. We may request information from you about your personal hair styling and fashion tastes and your hobbies or other related hair care and fashion related interests. This information will be requested from you directly and openly, and responding to such requests will be voluntary. Using the information you voluntarily give us, we may contact you with information or special offers. We will not require you to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in an activity as a condition of participation. All information submitted through [www.hash-master.com](http://www.hash-master.com/) will be held in the strictest of confidence and HASH MASTER does not share your personal information with 3rd parties without your permission. HASH MASTER does not sell our customer name and address lists. The information provided by you to us will be used only for the purposes of completing commercial activities with you and keeping you informed regarding HASH MASTER updates. We do not knowingly collect or use any personal information from children (minors younger than 13). If you are a parent and believe we may have inadvertently collected such information from your child, please notify us immediately by sending an email to [sales@hash-master.com](mailto:sales@hash-master.com) .

LINKS

For your convenience, [www.hash-master.com](http://www.hash-master.com/) may contain links to other websites. HASH MASTER is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
